<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 11:14:54 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming language</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/programminglanguage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 11:14:54 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/programminglanguage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;programming-language&#34;&gt;Programming Language&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- A formalized language designed to describe programs and algorithms for solving problems on a computer. Programming languages ​​are artificial. In them, the syntax and semantics are strictly demanding. Therefore, they do not allow free interpretation of statements, which is typical for natural language. Programming languages ​​are changing into two main categories of high-level languages ​​and high-level language:
- High-level language - A programming language whose means provide a description of the problem in a visual, easily perceived form, convenient for the programmer. It does not depend on the internal machine codes of any type of computer, so programs written in high-level languages ​​require translation into machine codes by translator or interpreter programs. High-level languages ​​include Fortran, PL / 1, BASIC, Pascal, C, Ada, etc.
- Low-level language - A programming language designed for a particular type of computer and reflecting its internal machine code (see also “machine language”, “machine-oriented language” and “assembler language” below).
&lt;h1 id=&#34;several-types-of-programming-languages&#34;&gt;Several types of programming languages&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- Algorithmic language - A set of symbols, conventions and rules used to unambiguously describe algorithms and is usually part of a programming language;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nonalgorithmic language - A programming language, the texts of which do not contain instructions on the order in which operations are performed and serve only as source material for the synthesis of an algorithm for solving a problem;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Source language - The programming language in which the program is written, as opposed to the machine language in which programs are executed by the computer. Source languages ​​are classified into high level languages ​​and low level languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machine (absolute) language, computer language - A programming language designed to represent programs in a form that makes it possible to execute them by technical means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Week 16.05-22.05</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 11:04:21 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/week03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;developments&#34;&gt;Developments&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- The past week has not been particularly remarkable. It was still chilly outside, even though it was almost summer outside. I spent most of my time sitting at home and watching TV shows. 
&lt;h1 id=&#34;cat&#34;&gt;Cat&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We have finally trimmed our Maine Coon cat. Now he has less wool by 80%. Perhaps this is the most important news.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;study&#34;&gt;Study&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I also did laboratory work for my studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with bibliography</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 20:29:22 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/bibliography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;working-with-bibliography&#34;&gt;Working with bibliography&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- The Word object model includes several objects designed to automate the creation of bibliographies. The following table lists the main objects of the Word Bibliography feature. 
- Use these objects and additional properties and methods in the Word object model to add sources to source lists, reference sources in a document, and manage sources. 
&lt;h1 id=&#34;understanding-the-xml-source&#34;&gt;Understanding the XML Source&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- Sources are added to source lists programmatically using XML strings. Depending on the type of source to be added, the XML structure changes. To define the XML structure for a source type, you can manually add the same source type and then view the returned XML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 09.05-15.05</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 20:17:37 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/week02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;victory-day&#34;&gt;Victory Day&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
Last week we celebrated Victory Day. That day I went to watch the parade and fireworks.
&lt;h1 id=&#34;news&#34;&gt;News&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
- Also last week my sister came to see me. We haven&#39;t seen each other for six months. So I was very glad that she came to me.
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 04:21:01 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-markdown&#34;&gt;About Markdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Markdown is a lightweight markup language for creating formatted text using a plain-text editor. John Gruber and Aaron Swartz created Markdown in 2004 as a markup language that is appealing to human readers in its source code form. Markdown is widely used in blogging, instant messaging, online forums, collaborative software, documentation pages, and readme files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2002 Aaron Swartz created atx, &amp;ldquo;the true structured text format&amp;rdquo;. Swartz and Gruber then worked together to create the Markdown language in 2004, with the goal of enabling people &amp;ldquo;to write using an easy-to-read and easy-to-write plain text format, optionally convert it to structurally valid XHTML.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ts key design goal was readability, that the language be readable as-is, without looking like it has been marked up with tags or formatting instructions, unlike text formatted with a markup language, such as Rich Text Format (RTF) or HTML, which have obvious tags and formatting instructions. To this end, its main inspiration is the existing conventions for marking up plain text in email, though it also draws from earlier markup languages, notably setext, Textile, and reStructuredText.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;standardization&#34;&gt;Standardization&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From 2012, a group of people, including Jeff Atwood and John MacFarlane, launched what Atwood characterised as a standardisation effort. A community website now aims to &amp;ldquo;document various tools and resources available to document authors and developers, as well as implementors of the various Markdown implementations&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In September 2014, Gruber objected to the usage of &amp;ldquo;Markdown&amp;rdquo; in the name of this effort and it was rebranded as CommonMark. CommonMark.org published several versions of a specification, reference implementation, test suite, and &amp;quot; to announce a finalized 1.0 spec and test suite in 2019.&amp;rdquo; No 1.0 spec has since been released as major issues still remain unsolved. Nonetheless, the following sites and projects have adopted CommonMark: Discourse, GitHub, GitLab, Reddit, Qt, Stack Exchange (Stack Overflow), and Swift.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last week</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/lastweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 04:05:12 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/lastweek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;events&#34;&gt;Events&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
-  During the May holidays, I spent my time very interestingly. I walked a lot with my friends, went to the pool, read and did not sleep until the morning. I also did laboratory work on the subject &#34;Operating systems&#34;. 
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I really wanted to go to my parents for the weekend, but unfortunately there were not so many weekends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My last week was fun and interesting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Wowchemy, the website builder for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Wowchemy website builder for Hugo, along with its starter templates, is designed for professional creators, educators, and teams/organizations - although it can be used to create any kind of site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The template can be modified and customised to suit your needs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good platform for anyone looking to take control of their data and online identity whilst having the convenience to start off with a &lt;strong&gt;no-code solution (write in Markdown and customize with YAML parameters)&lt;/strong&gt; and having &lt;strong&gt;flexibility to later add even deeper personalization with HTML and CSS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can work with all your favourite tools and apps with hundreds of plugins and integrations to speed up your workflows, interact with your readers, and much more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
















&lt;figure  id=&#34;figure-the-template-is-mobile-first-with-a-responsive-design-to-ensure-that-your-site-looks-stunning-on-every-device&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/master/academic.png&#34; alt=&#34;The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      The template is mobile first with a responsive design to ensure that your site looks stunning on every device.
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started&#34;&gt;Get Started&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;👉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/templates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a new site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📚 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalize your site&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💬 &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/z8wNYzb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Chat with the &lt;strong&gt;Wowchemy community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hugo community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🐦 Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/wowchemy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/GeorgeCushen&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;@GeorgeCushen&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MadeWithWowchemy&amp;amp;src=typed_query&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;#MadeWithWowchemy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;💡 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Request a &lt;strong&gt;feature&lt;/strong&gt; or report a &lt;strong&gt;bug&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;em&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⬆️ &lt;strong&gt;Updating Wowchemy?&lt;/strong&gt; View the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/hugo-tutorials/update/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Update Tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/updates/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;crowd-funded-open-source-software&#34;&gt;Crowd-funded open-source software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help us develop this template and software sustainably under the MIT license, we ask all individuals and businesses that use it to help support its ongoing maintenance and development via sponsorship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-click-here-to-become-a-sponsor-and-help-support-wowchemys-future-httpswowchemycomplans&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;❤️ Click here to become a sponsor and help support Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s future ❤️&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a token of appreciation for sponsoring, you can &lt;strong&gt;unlock &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/plans/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; awesome rewards and extra features 🦄✨&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ecosystem&#34;&gt;Ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/hugo-academic-cli&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Hugo Academic CLI&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Automatically import publications from BibTeX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration&#34;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Check out the latest &lt;strong&gt;demo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/user-stories/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;view the &lt;strong&gt;showcase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of personal, project, and business sites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Page builder&lt;/strong&gt; - Create &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/page-builder/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;widgets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;elements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit any type of content&lt;/strong&gt; - Blog posts, publications, talks, slides, projects, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create content&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/content/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/import/jupyter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jupyter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/install-locally/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RStudio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System&lt;/strong&gt; - Fully customizable &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;color&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font themes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Display Code and Math&lt;/strong&gt; - Code highlighting and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LaTeX math&lt;/a&gt; supported&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrations&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://analytics.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Disqus commenting&lt;/a&gt;, Maps, Contact Forms, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beautiful Site&lt;/strong&gt; - Simple and refreshing one page design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry-Leading SEO&lt;/strong&gt; - Help get your website found on search engines and social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media Galleries&lt;/strong&gt; - Display your images and videos with captions in a customizable gallery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Friendly&lt;/strong&gt; - Look amazing on every screen with a mobile friendly version of your site&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-language&lt;/strong&gt; - 34+ language packs including English, 中文, and Português&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-user&lt;/strong&gt; - Each author gets their own profile page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Pack&lt;/strong&gt; - Assists with GDPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stand Out&lt;/strong&gt; - Bring your site to life with animation, parallax backgrounds, and scroll effects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Click Deployment&lt;/strong&gt; - No servers. No databases. Only files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wowchemy and its templates come with &lt;strong&gt;automatic day (light) and night (dark) mode&lt;/strong&gt; built-in. Alternatively, visitors can choose their preferred mode - click the moon icon in the top right of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt; to see it in action! Day/night mode can also be disabled by the site admin in &lt;code&gt;params.toml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/customization&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Choose a stunning &lt;strong&gt;theme&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;font&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for your site. Themes are fully customizable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2016-present &lt;a href=&#34;https://georgecushen.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;George Cushen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Released under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/blob/master/LICENSE.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;MIT&lt;/a&gt; license.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
