<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>markdown | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/markdown/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>markdown</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 04:21:01 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>markdown</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/markdown/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 04:21:01 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-markdown&#34;&gt;About Markdown&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Markdown is a lightweight markup language for creating formatted text using a plain-text editor. John Gruber and Aaron Swartz created Markdown in 2004 as a markup language that is appealing to human readers in its source code form. Markdown is widely used in blogging, instant messaging, online forums, collaborative software, documentation pages, and readme files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;history&#34;&gt;History&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2002 Aaron Swartz created atx, &amp;ldquo;the true structured text format&amp;rdquo;. Swartz and Gruber then worked together to create the Markdown language in 2004, with the goal of enabling people &amp;ldquo;to write using an easy-to-read and easy-to-write plain text format, optionally convert it to structurally valid XHTML.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ts key design goal was readability, that the language be readable as-is, without looking like it has been marked up with tags or formatting instructions, unlike text formatted with a markup language, such as Rich Text Format (RTF) or HTML, which have obvious tags and formatting instructions. To this end, its main inspiration is the existing conventions for marking up plain text in email, though it also draws from earlier markup languages, notably setext, Textile, and reStructuredText.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;standardization&#34;&gt;Standardization&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From 2012, a group of people, including Jeff Atwood and John MacFarlane, launched what Atwood characterised as a standardisation effort. A community website now aims to &amp;ldquo;document various tools and resources available to document authors and developers, as well as implementors of the various Markdown implementations&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In September 2014, Gruber objected to the usage of &amp;ldquo;Markdown&amp;rdquo; in the name of this effort and it was rebranded as CommonMark. CommonMark.org published several versions of a specification, reference implementation, test suite, and &amp;quot; to announce a finalized 1.0 spec and test suite in 2019.&amp;rdquo; No 1.0 spec has since been released as major issues still remain unsolved. Nonetheless, the following sites and projects have adopted CommonMark: Discourse, GitHub, GitLab, Reddit, Qt, Stack Exchange (Stack Overflow), and Swift.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
